<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.audiotube</id>
  <name>AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxAudioTubexx</name>
  <summary>Convergent YouTube Music client</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Client convergent per a la música de YouTube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Client convergent per a la música de YouTube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Konvergentes YouTube-Musikprogramm</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Cliente de música de YouTube convergente</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">올인원 YouTube Music 클라이언트</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Convergente muziekclient van YouTube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Konvergent YouTube-musikprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Зручний музичний клієнт YouTube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxConvergent YouTube Music clientxx</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <developer_name>KDE Community</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">La comunitat KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca-valencia">La comunitat KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="de">KDE-Gemeinschaft</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">Comunidad KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ko">KDE 커뮤니티</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">KDE-gemeenschap</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sv">KDE-gemenskapen</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Спільнота KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Communityxx</developer_name>
  <description>
    <p>AudioTube can search YouTube Music, list albums and artists, play automatically generated playlists, albums and allows to put your own playlist together.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'AudioTube pot cercar música a YouTube, llistar àlbums i artistes, reproduir llistes de reproducció generades automàticament, àlbums i permet crear la vostra pròpia llista de reproducció.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'AudioTube pot cercar música a YouTube, llistar àlbums i artistes, reproduir llistes de reproducció generades automàticament, àlbums i permet crear la vostra pròpia llista de reproducció.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">AudioTube kann Musik auf YouTube durchsuchen, Alben und Interpreten auflisten, automatisch generierte Wiedergabelisten und Alben abspielen und erlaubt es, eine eigene Wiedergabeliste zusammenzustellen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">AudioTube puede buscar música de YouTube, listar álbumes y artistas, reproducir las listas de reproducción generadas, álbumes y le permite crear su propia lista de reproducción.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">AudioTube는 YouTube Music을 검색하고, 앨범과 아티스트를 표시하고, 자동 생성된 재생 목록, 앨범을 재생하고, 사용자 정의 재생 목록을 만들 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">AudioTube kan in YouTube Music zoeken, een lijst maken van albums en artiesten, automatically gegenereerde afspeellijsten, albums afspelen en biedt u het samenstellen van uw eigen afspeellijst.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">AudioTube kan söka på YouTube Music, lista album och artister, spela upp automatiskt genererade spellistor, albums och låter dig sammanställa egna spellistor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">AudioTube може виконувати пошук на YouTube Music, показувати списки альбомів та виконавців, відтворювати створені автоматично списки відтворення, альбоми та надає вам змогу створювати власні списки відворення.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxAudioTube can search YouTube Music, list albums and artists, play automatically generated playlists, albums and allows to put your own playlist together.xx</p>
  </description>
</component>
