<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2021 Jonah Brüchert <jbb@kaidan.im>

SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
-->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.audiotube</id>
  <name>AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">تيوب الصوتي</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="az">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">ओडियो-ट्यूब</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਆਡੀਓ-ਟਿਊਬ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="sa">ऑडियोट्यूब</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxAudioTubexx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">AudioTube</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">AudioTube</name>
  <summary>YouTube Music app</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">تطبيق يوتيوب ميوزيك</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Aplicació de YouTube Music</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Aplicació de YouTube Music</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Přehrávač hudby YouTube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">YouTube-Musikprogramm</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">YouTube Music app</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">YouTube Music-apo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Aplicación de música de YouTube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">YouTube Music aplikazioa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">YouTube Music -sovellus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Application de musique sur YouTube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Aplicación de música de YouTube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">יישום YouTube Music</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">YouTube Music alkalmazás</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">App de Musica de YouTube (YouTube Music)</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Aplikasi YouTube Music</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Applicazione YouTube Music</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">YouTube Music-ის აპი</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">YouTube Music 앱</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">„YouTube Music“ programa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">„YouTube Music“ programma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Muziektoepassing van YouTube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">YouTube Music-app</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Aplikacja do muzyki z YouTuba</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Aplicativo de música pro YouTube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Приложение для работы с YouTube Music</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sa">YouTube Music app</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Aplikacija za glasbo YouTube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">YouTube musikprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">YouTube Müzik Uygulaması</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Музична програма для YouTube</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxYouTube Music appxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">YouTube 音乐应用</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">YouTube Music 應用程式</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0"/>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/en/audiotube</url>
  <developer id="org.kde">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <releases>
    <release version="25.08.1" date="2025-09-11"/>
    <release version="25.08.0" date="2025-08-14"/>
    <release version="25.04.3" date="2025-07-03"/>
    <release version="25.04.2" date="2025-06-05"/>
    <release version="25.04.1" date="2025-05-08"/>
    <release version="25.04.0" date="2025-04-17"/>
    <release version="24.12.3" date="2025-03-06"/>
    <release version="24.12.2" date="2025-02-06"/>
    <release version="24.12.1" date="2025-01-09"/>
    <release version="24.12.0" date="2024-12-12"/>
    <release version="24.08.3" date="2024-11-07"/>
    <release version="24.08.2" date="2024-10-10"/>
    <release version="24.08.1" date="2024-09-12"/>
    <release version="24.08.0" date="2024-08-22"/>
    <release version="24.05.2" date="2024-07-04"/>
    <release version="24.05.1" date="2024-06-13"/>
    <release version="24.05.0" date="2024-05-23"/>
    <release version="24.02.2" date="2024-04-11"/>
    <release version="24.02.1" date="2024-03-21"/>
    <release version="24.02.0" date="2024-02-28"/>
    <release version="23.08.5" date="2024-02-15"/>
    <release version="23.08.4" date="2023-12-07"/>
    <release version="23.08.3" date="2023-11-09"/>
    <release version="23.08.2" date="2023-10-12"/>
    <release version="23.08.1" date="2023-09-14"/>
    <release version="23.08.0" date="2023-08-24"/>
    <release version="23.04.3" date="2023-07-06"/>
    <release version="23.04.2" date="2023-06-08"/>
    <release version="23.04.1" date="2023-05-11"/>
    <release version="23.04.0" date="2023-04-20"/>
    <release version="23.01" date="2023-01-30">
      <url>https://plasma-mobile.org/2023/01/30/january-blog-post/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="22.11" date="2022-11-30">
      <url>https://plasma-mobile.org/2022/11/30/plasma-mobile-gear-22-11/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="22.09" date="2022-09-27">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2022/09/27/plasma-mobile-gear-22-09/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="22.06" date="2022-06-24">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2022/06/28/plasma-mobile-gear-22-06/</url>
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Add library page which shows favourites and most played songs</li>
          <li>Improve layout of the search popup</li>
          <li>General performance improvements including startup</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.04" date="2022-04-26">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2022/04/26/plasma-mobile-gear-22-04/</url>
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Update the version of ytmusicapi</li>
          <li>General code-refactoring and translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.02" date="2022-02-09">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2022/02/09/plasma-mobile-gear-22-02/</url>
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Update the version of ytmusicapi</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.12" date="2021-12-07">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2021/12/07/plasma-mobile-gear-21-12/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="21.08" date="2021-08-31">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2021/08/31/plasma-mobile-gear-21-08/</url>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.audiotube.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/audiotube/library.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/audiotube/player.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/audiotube/desktop.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/audiotube/mobile_album.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/audiotube/mobile_playlist.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <recommends>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </recommends>
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
  </requires>
  <description>
    <p>AudioTube can search YouTube Music, list albums and artists, play automatically generated playlists, albums and allows to put your own playlist together. It is adapted to mobile phones and desktop computers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يمكن لتيوب الصوتي البحث في موسيقى يوتيوب، وعرض الألبومات والفنانين، وتشغيل القوائم والألبومات المولدة آليًّا، ويسمح لك بوضع قائمة التشغيل الخاصة بك معًا. هو ملائم للهواتف المحمولة وأجهزة الحاسوب المكتبية.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'AudioTube pot cercar a YouTube Music, llistar àlbums i artistes, reproduir llistes de reproducció generades automàticament, àlbums i permet crear la vostra pròpia llista de reproducció. Està adaptat als telèfons mòbils i els ordinadors de sobretaula.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">AudioTube pot buscar a YouTube Music, llistar àlbums i artistes, reproduir llistes de reproducció generades automàticament, àlbums i permet crear la vostra pròpia llista de reproducció. Està adaptat als telèfons mòbils i els ordinadors de sobretaula.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">AudioTube kann Musik auf YouTube durchsuchen, Alben und Interpreten auflisten, automatisch generierte Wiedergabelisten und Alben abspielen und erlaubt es, eine eigene Wiedergabeliste zusammenzustellen. Mobiltelefone und Desktoprechner werden unterstützt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">AudioTube can search YouTube Music, list albums and artists, play automatically generated playlists, albums and allows to put your own playlist together. It is adapted to mobile phones and desktop computers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">AudioTube povas serĉi YouTube Music, listigi albumojn kaj artistojn, ludi aŭtomate generitajn ludlistojn, albumojn kaj permesas kunmeti vian propran ludliston. Ĝi estas adaptita al porteblaj telefonoj kaj labortablaj komputiloj.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">AudioTube puede buscar música de YouTube, listar álbumes y artistas, reproducir las listas de reproducción generadas, álbumes y le permite crear su propia lista de reproducción. Está adaptada para teléfonos móviles y equipos de escritorio.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">«AudioTube»k «YouTube Music»en bilatu dezake, albumak eta artistak zerrendatu, automatikoki sortutako jotze-zerrendak eta albumak jo, eta zure jotze-zerrenda osatzeko aukera eskaintzen dizu. Telefono mugikorretarako eta mahaigaineko ordenagailuetarako moldatuta dago.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">AudioTube osaa etsiä YouTube Musicista, luetella albumit ja artistit, toistaa automaattisesti luotuja ja koota omia soittolistoja. Se sopii niin mobiililaitteisiin kuin tietokoneisiinkin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">L'application AudioTube peut rechercher des musiques, d'établir des listes d'albums et d'artistes, de lire des listes de lecture générées automatiquement. Elle permet aussi d'utiliser sa propre liste de lecture. Elle est adaptée aux téléphones mobiles et aux ordinateurs de bureau.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">AudioTube pode buscar en YouTube Music, listar álbums e intérpretes, reproducir listas xeradas automaticamente e álbums, e permítelle confeccionar listas. Está adaptada para teléfonos móbiles e computadores de escritorio.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">AudioTube יכול לחפש ב־YouTube Music, להציג אלבומים ואומנים, לנגן רשימות נגינה ואלובומים שנוצרו אוטומטית, ומאפשר לך להרכיב רשימות נגינה משלך. הוא מותאם לטלפונים ניידים ולמחשבים.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Az AudioTube képes a YouTube Music keresésére, albumok és előadók listázására, automatikusan generált lejátszási listák és albumok lejátszására, valamint lehetővé teszi saját lejátszási lista összeállítását. Mobiltelefonokon és asztali számítógépeken egyaránt működik.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">AudioTube pote cercar in YouTube Music, listar albums e artistas, reproducer listas de reproduction generate automaticamente, albums e te permitte poner  tu proprie lista de reproduction insimul. Il es adaptate a telephonos mobile e computatiores de scriptorio.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">AudioTube dapat mencari YouTube Music, daftar album dan artis, putar playlist yang dibuat secara otomatis, album dan memungkinkan Anda untuk menyusun playlist Anda sendiri. Aplikasi ini disesuaikan untuk ponsel dan komputer desktop.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">AudioTube può eseguire ricerche su YouTube Music, elencare album e artisti, riprodurre scalette e album generati automaticamente e ti consente di creare la tua scaletta. È adatto ai telefoni cellulari e ai computer desktop.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">AudioTube -ს შეუძლია მოძებნოს მუსიკა YouTube-ზე, გაჩვენოთ ალბომებისა და შემსრულებლების სია, დაუკრას დაგენერირებული დასაკრავი სიები, ალბომები და საშუალებას გაძლევთ, თქვენი დასაკრავი სია შექმნათ. ის მორგებულია მობილურ კომპიუტერებზე და ნოუთბუქებზე.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">AudioTube는 YouTube Music을 검색하고, 앨범과 아티스트를 표시하고, 자동 생성된 재생 목록, 앨범을 재생하고, 사용자 정의 재생 목록을 만들 수 있습니다. 휴대폰과 데스크톱 컴퓨터 둘 다에서 사용할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">AudioTube gali atlikti paiešką „YouTube Music“, išvardyti albumus ir atlikėjus, atkurti automatiškai sugeneruotus grojaraščius, albumus ir leidžia sudaryti savo asmeninį grojaraštį. AudioTube yra pritaikyta kompiuteriams bei mobiliesiems telefonams.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Ar „AudioTube“ varat meklēt „YouTube Music“, uzskaitīt albumus un izpildītājus, atskaņot automātiski izveidotus repertuārus, albumus un veidot savu repertuāru. Programma ir piemērota lietošanai mobilajos tālruņos un datoros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">AudioTube kan in YouTube Music zoeken, een lijst maken van albums en artiesten, automatically gegenereerde afspeellijsten, albums afspelen en biedt u het samenstellen van uw eigen afspeellijst. Het is aangepast aan mobiele telefoons en bureaubladcomputers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Med AudioTube kan du søkja på YouTube Music, visa album og artistar, spela automatiske genererte spelelister og album samt laga eigne spelelister. Programmet er tilpassa både mobiltelefonar og datamaskiner.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">AudioTube może przeszukiwać serwis YouTube Music, wypisać albumy i wykonawców, odtwarzać samoczynnie utworzone listy odtwarzania, albumy oraz umożliwia tworzenie własnych list odtwarzania. Jest dostosowana do telefonów i komputerów.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">adaptedO AudioTube pode pesquisar no YouTube Music, listar álbuns e artistas, rodar listas de reprodução geradas automaticamente, álbuns inteiros, e criar a sua própria lista de reprodução. Ele é adaptado para celulares e computadores.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">AudioTube позволяет выполнять поиск в сервисе YouTube Music, просматривать списки найденных альбомов и исполнителей, воспроизводить автоматически созданные списки воспроизведения и альбомы, а также составлять свои собственные списки воспроизведения. Приложение адаптировано для работы на мобильных телефонах и настольных компьютерах.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">AudioTube YouTube Music अन्वेष्टुं शक्नोति, एल्बमान् कलाकारान् च सूचीतुं शक्नोति, स्वयमेव उत्पन्नं प्लेलिस्ट्, एल्बम् वादयितुं शक्नोति तथा च स्वस्य प्लेलिस्ट् एकत्र स्थापयितुं शक्नोति। इदं मोबाईलफोनेषु, डेस्कटॉप् सङ्गणकेषु च अनुकूलितम् अस्ति ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">AudioTube lahko išče YouTube Music, navaja albume in izvajalce, predvaja samodejno ustvarjene sezname predvajanja, albume in omogoča sestavljanje lastnega seznama predvajanja. Prilagojena je mobilnim telefonom in namiznim računalnikom.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">AudioTube kan söka på YouTube Music, lista album och artister, spela upp automatiskt genererade spellistor, album och låter dig sammanställa egna spellistor. Det är anpassat för mobiltelefoner och skrivbordsdatorer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">AudioTube, YouTube Müzik’te arama yapabilir; albümleri, sanatçıları listeler; kendiliğinden üretilmiş çalma listelerini, albümleri çalar ve kendi çalma listenizi oluşturmanıza izin verir. Masaüstü bilgisayarlar ve cep telefonları için uyarlanmıştır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">AudioTube може виконувати пошук на YouTube Music, показувати списки альбомів та виконавців, відтворювати створені автоматично списки відтворення, альбоми та надає вам змогу створювати власні списки відтворення. Програму адаптовано до мобільних телефонів та робочих станцій.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxAudioTube can search YouTube Music, list albums and artists, play automatically generated playlists, albums and allows to put your own playlist together. It is adapted to mobile phones and desktop computers.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">AudioTube 可以搜索 YouTube Music 的内容，列出专辑和艺人，播放自动生成的播放列表，还可以自行制作播放列表。适用于手机和台式电脑。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">AudioTube 可以搜尋 YouTube Music、列出專輯與藝人、播放專輯或自動產生的播放清單，也讓您建立自己的播放清單。它同時設計給行動裝置與桌面電腦使用。</p>
  </description>
  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#f19a9a</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#5a0c0c</color>
  </branding>
  <custom>
    <value key="KDE::supporters">Alessio Adamo</value>
  </custom>
</component>
